(Penny:)inflamed heart is only
a "mild side effect." (laughs)
(Second Girl:)I heard you can make
good money doing that.
(Penny:)Yeah, it's going okay,
but I do miss this sometimes.
(Leonard:)Really?
Mmm.
'Cause I got to tell
you, I am so sick
(First Girl:)of the humiliation and being
treated like a piece of meat.
(Audiitoner:)Chelsea?
Wish me luck. (laughs)
(Second Girl:)They're gonna
love you.
(Second Girl:)I heard she's pushing 40
and everything's fake.
(Penny:)Yeah. I started
that rumor.
(Leonard:)Okay, since we agree
on the delivery system
(Raj:)for the message,
maybe we should talk
(Leonard:)about what the message could be.
(Raj:)Well, I think we should show
what earthlings look like.
(Howard:)The plaque they sent up on the
Pioneer probe had a drawing
(Howard:)of a naked man
and woman on it.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, I never cared for that.
(Sheldon:)It's advertising
to predator races
(Sheldon:)just how soft
and squishy we are.
Squeeze yourself!
(Sheldon:)Oh, don't be offended.
(Sheldon:)You know, of
the four of us,
(Sheldon:)you have the most
veal-like consistency.